bluestarindia.com 2019-05-10

# Privacy Policy

Blue Star Limited (“BSL”) recognises the importance of maintaining your privacy. This Policy describes how we treat user information we collect on our website. This Privacy Policy applies to current and former visitors to our website and to our online customers. By visiting and/or using our website, you agree to this Privacy Policy.

BSL provide adequate safeguards where such information is processed in the way of including but not limited to collection, recording, storing, utilisation, disclosure, transfer and deletion. BSL processes the data fairly in compliance with the applicable laws.

Information We Collect

_Non-Personally Identifiable Information:_

Non-personally identifiable information is information that, by itself, cannot be tracked to a specific individual. BSL may collect non-personally identifiable information while you are visiting the Site.

While providing services and features, BSL may collect web surfing data such as your IP address, web pages on the Site that have you visited, time and date, We use different types of technologies to collect this information, including cookies and single-pixel GIFs.

If your browser is configured to accept the cookies, these cookies will be used to recognise your computer when you revisit the Site to provide you with a superior user experience to help you improve performance. However, if you wish, you can configure your browser to block cookies.

_Personally Identifiable Information:_

While providing various products, services or features, we may ask you to provide personal information. For example, you may be asked to provide your name, age, gender, email address, telephone number, address, preferences and other details.

We may ask for similar information at other times including during promotions sponsored by BSL or its affiliates.

We may also collect information relating to products and services provided to you, including details of requests you may have made, the products and services we may have provided, their delivery, billing and invoicing, any communication or correspondence with you, and other transactional information. We may also record your communication with our customer care or with other such contact points, in accordance with applicable law.

Use of the Information We Collect

BSL does not intentionally provide personally identifiable information to third parties except under the following conditions:

If you provide personally identifiable information as part of an inquiry about products or services provided by one of the advertisers or employees or while participating in any promotional offers provided by BSL from time to time, we will provide that information to that advertiser or employee or sponsor or co-sponsor of the promotional event so that they may attempt to provide you with information regarding the products or services or promotional offer about which you inquired, BSL may use the personally identifiable information provided by users for credit reporting, compilation of a transaction, internal purposes, such as sales, human resources, marketing, and administration. Further personally identifiable information may be provided by BSL to any statutory authorities or to any regulatory body in accordance with laws governing BSL.

Security

BSL makes significant efforts to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the collected information. These measures may include the use of secure server technology. Be aware, however, that the Internet is not completely secure. Therefore, we cannot ensure the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet, and we accept no liability for any unintentional disclosure.

Some areas of our website may be password-protected. To increase security, please do not share your passwords with anyone. You shall not undertake any act which amounts to breach of security and you shall not try to access password-protected area of the Site without proper authorisation.

Grievance

Provider of information may raise grievance to the following e-mail ID:

itprivacygrievance@bluestarindia.com

All the grievances and any discrepancies of the provider of information shall be redressed within one month (30 days) from the date of receipt of notice of grievance.

Modification

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. Please check the effective date at the bottom of this page to determine if the privacy policy has been modified since you last reviewed it. We also will notify you about significant changes to the privacy policy by sending you a notice to the primary email address specified in your account or by placing a prominent notice on the Site. Your continued use of our site following posting of the updated privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.

Jurisdiction and Governing Law

Any disputes arising under or connected with this Policy shall be governed by the laws of India and courts of Mumbai shall have exclusive jurisdiction for any dispute arising under or connected with this policy.

Acceptance of Privacy Policy

BY USING OUR WEBSITE, YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE PRACTICES SET OUT IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR TERMS OF USE AGREEMENT.
